Guide to the Charles McKinney Papers, 1952-1993 and undated RL.00878
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Account Files, 1968-1990 and undated, 17 boxes
  - Gravely
    - Lawn and garden marketing magazine reports, 1974-1975 (Box 13)
    - Positioning strategy, 1976, undated (Box 13)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 13)
    - Presentation notes, undated (Box 13)
    - Situation summary, undated (Box 13)
    - Strategy overview, undated (Box 13)
    - Three year marketing plan, 1975-1977 (Box 13)
    - Trade media program, undated (Box 13)
  - Hallmark (Box 14)
    - New products proposal, undated (Box 14)
  - Hanes, Cargill, Willson & Acree, Inc.
    - Marketing plan for new hosiery brand, undated (Box 14)
    - New business, 1966-1967 (Box 14)
  - Harcourt Brace Jovanovich
    - Florida Parks, general presentation, 1987 (Box 14)
  - Heinz
    - Presentation, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Holly Farms
    - Clippings, 1977 and undated (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1977 (Box 14)
    - Presentation, 1977 (Box 14)
    - Presentation appendix, undated (Box 14)
  - Homelite
    - Clippings, 1975 (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1975, 1983 (Box 14)
    - Flip chart presentation, undated (Box 14)
    - Presentation, M&S introduction, undated (Box 14)
    - Presentation notes, undated (Box 14)
    - Presentation, Why Homelite Corporation Should Retain M&S, undated (Box 14)
    - Proposal, undated, 3 folders (Box 14)
  - Jim Dandy Chunx Dog Food, Cargill, Wilson & Acree, Inc. (Box 15)
    - Presentation, 1967 (Box 15)
  - Karastan-Bigelow Carpets
    - Presentation, undated (Box 15)
    - [Proofs removed to Oversize Materials) (Box 15)
  - Kingsdown
    - Ad scripts, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Advertising program recommendations, 1973 (Box 15)
    - Guidelines for Establishing Kingsdown Brand Name, 1976 (Box 15)
    - Memos and Correspondence, 1975-1978, 2 folders (Box 15)
    - Presentation, undated (Box 15)
    - Presentation notes, undated (Box 15)
    - Proofs and tearsheets, undated (Box 15)
    - Reference materials, 1973-1974 (Box 15)
    - Summary analysis and 1975 advertising recommendation, 1974 (Box 15)
  - Leader Savings & Loan, McDonald & Little
    - Presentation, 1975 (Box 15)
  - Mars, Inc.
    - Flip chart, undated (Box 15)
    - Presentation, Competing with the Giants, 1983 (Box 15)
    - Presentation, Survival in the Sea of Video Tape, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Mastercharge
    - Market summary, undated (Box 16)
  - McDonald's
    - Presentation, 1976 (Box 16)
  - Monk-Austin Holding Company
    - Name development, undated (Box 16)
  - Nitrex
    - Proofs, undated (Box 16)
  - North Carolina National Bank
    - General files, 1983 and undated (Box 16)
    - Brand positioning, 1988 (Box 16)
    - Briefing report, undated (Box 16)
    - Campaign sketches and drafts, undated (Box 16)
    - Communications plan, 1988 (Box 16)
    - Creative marketing concept, undated (Box 16)
    - Introductory presentation, 1974 (Box 16)
    - Promotional booklet, undated (Box 16)
    - Proposals, 1989-1990 (Box 16)
    - Proposed marketing direction, 1971 (Box 16)
  - North Carolina Travel and Tourism
    - Proofs, undated (Some items removed to Oversize Materials) (Box 16)
  - Norweigan Cruise Line (Box 17)
    - Agency agreement, 1986 (Box 17)
    - Brand review, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Brochures, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Creative brief, 1989 (Box 17)
    - Creative presentation, 1988 (Box 17)
    - Proofs, undated (Box 17)
  - Orkin Extermination, Cargill, Wilson & Acree, Inc.
    - Marketing proposal, 1967, 2 folders (Box 17)
  - PET Dairy
    - Agency presentation, 1985 (Box 17)
    - Annual report, 1970 (Box 17)
    - Proposals, undated (Box 17)
    - Reference, 1968-1970 (Box 17)
  - Picadilly Circles
    - Proposal, undated (Box 17)
  - Piedmont Airlines (Box 18)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 18)
    - Compiled data, 1984 (Box 18)
    - Competitive
      - Espley & Espley presentation, 1986 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous tearsheets, undated (Box 18)
    - Conference reports, 1980-1985 (Box 18)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1983 (Box 18)
    - Frequent flyer bonus program, 1985 (Box 18)
    - Market share growth charts, 1981 (Box 18)
    - Meetings
      - Business traveler media discussion, 1986 (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous meetings, 1985 and undated (Box 18)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 18)
    - Presentations
      - How to Make Your Employees Care About Your Airline, undated (Box 18)
      - Media proposals, Launch and Follow-up campaign, London-Charlotte route, undated (Box 18)
      - Miscellaneous presentations, 1984 and undated (Box 18)
      - Orlando managers meeting, undated (Box 18)
      - Piedmont: The Up and Coming Airline, 1980 (Box 19)
      - Planning: 1985 and Beyond, 1986 (Box 19)
      - 1986 Presentation, 1986 (Box 19)
    - Press, 1979-1990 and undated (Some items removed to Oversize Materials), 2 folders (Box 19)
    - Printed material, 1979 and undated (Box 19)
    - Proof book
      - Table of contents for all volumes, undated (Box 19)
      - Vol. XXVIII, 1987, 2 folders (Box 19)
      - Vol. XXIX, undated (Box 19)
    - Proposals: Baltimore-Washington international hub, undated (Box 19)
    - Response to questionnaire, 1979 (Box 19)
    - Selected operating data, 1980-1982 (Box 20)
    - Status report, 1982 (Box 20)
  - Pillsbury
    - Consumer brands presentation, undated (Box 20)
    - Hidden Dimension of Attitudes, undated (Box 20)
    - Introduction to the American Beauty Division of the Pillsbury Company, undated (Box 20)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 20)
    - People and Food: The Shaping of a Market, undated (Box 20)
  - Pine State
    - General files, 1975 and undated (Box 20)
    - Client case history, undated (Box 20)
    - Proofs, undated (Some items removed to Oversize Materials) (Box 20)
  - Precision Tune
    - Introductory presentation, 1988 (Box 20)
  - Quincy's
    - Agency questionnaire, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Presentation, How We Would Approach An Assignment for Quincy's, undated (Box 20)
    - Restaurant prospects, 1986 (Box 20)
  - Raleigh-Belair
    - Presentation, Rebuilding the Raleigh-Belair Franchises, undated (Box 20)
  - Ralston Purina
    - Meeting materials, 1988 and undated (Box 20)
  - Red Band
    - General presentation, undated (Box 20)
  - Red Lobster
    - Presentation, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Royal Caribbean Cruise Line
    - Case history, undated (Box 20)
    - Case study, 1987 (Box 20)
    - Copy direction, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Crab mailer, undated (Box 20)
    - Media plan, 1984 (Box 20)
    - Memos and correspondence, 1982-1984 and undated (Box 20)
    - Presentations
      - Charts, undated (Box 20)
      - General presentation, undated (Box 20)
      - Making RCCL the Number One Cruise Line, undated (Box 20)
      - Structure of the Cruise Market, undated (Box 20)
    - Production estimates for 1983 program, 1982 (Box 20)
    - Proofs, 1982 and undated (Some items removed to Oversize Materials) (Box 21)
    - Proposal, 1982 (Box 21)
    - Status report, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Ryder Truck
    - Presentation, 1986 (Box 21)
    - Memos and correspondence, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Savannah Sugar Refining Company, Cargill, Wilson & Acree
    - Presentation, undated (Box 21)
  - Sea World
    - Presentation, 1987 (Box 21)
  - South Carolina National Bank
    - Introductory presentation, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Preliminary marketing proposal, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Sperry & Hutchinson Co. Furnishings Division, Mel Richman Inc.
    - Presentation, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Taco Bueno
    - General files, 1986 (Box 21)
  - Texize Chemicals
    - Introductory presentation, 1975 (Box 21)
  - Tile Council of America
    - Advertising plan for 1978, 1977 (Box 21)
    - Advertising schedules, 1978 (Box 21)
    - Long range marketing study, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Long range marketing study, research conclusions, 1974 (Box 21)
    - Presentation to Board of Directors, 1976 (Box 21)
    - Tile contractors survey, undated (Box 21)
  - Travelmation (Box 22)
    - Agency profile, 1986 (Box 22)
    - Memos and correspondence, 1985 (Box 22)
    - Presentation, 1986 (Box 22)
  - United Virginia Bank
    - Marketing planning commentary, 1977 (Box 22)
    - Strategic development plan, 1977 (Box 22)
  - USAir Group, Inc.
    - Presentations
      - Piedmont-USAir Group, Inc. merger, 1988 (Box 22)
      - Rough draft, undated (Box 22)
    - President's Night address, Edwin Colodny, 1988 (Box 22)
    - Proofs, undated (Some items removed to Oversize Materials) (Box 22)
    - Sketches, undated (Some items removed to Oversize Materials) (Box 22)
  - Valley National Bank
    - Copy direction, 1986 and undated (Box 22)
  - Virginia National Bank
    - Planning steps, phase one, undated (Box 22)
- Competitive Files, 1967-1989, 2 boxes
  Contains correspondence, printed materials, proofs and clippings related to competitive advertising agencies. Includes resumes, company profiles and brochures prepared by agencies, as well as presentations and pamphlets prepared on general marketing issues. Represented agencies include Ted Bates Agency; Howard Agency; Gold Greelees Trott; Doyle Dane Bernbach; Delehanty, Kurnit & Geller, Inc.; Campbell-Mithun, Inc.; Cargill, Wilson & Acree; Norman, Craig & Kummel; Ogilvy & Mather; John Rockwell & Associates; Scali, McCabe, Sloves; and Wells, Rich, Greene, Inc., among others. Items arrived loose and were grouped by agency and arranged alphabetically.
  - Bates Agency (Ted Bates), printed matter, undated (Box 23)
  - Campbell-Mithun, Inc., Managing New Products, Marketing Development, 1973 (Box 23)
  - Cargill, Wilson and Acree, Inc.
    - Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 23)
    - New business program, 1967-1968 (Box 23)
    - Resume, c. 1970 (Box 23)
  - Collett, Dickensen, Pearce & Partners, Ltd., brochure, undated (Box 23)
  - CFG, presentation, Improving Marketing Communications Through Positioning Development, 1979 (Box 23)
  - Delehanty, Kurnit & Geller, Inc., booklet, undated (Box 23)
  - Doyle Dane Bernbach, general files, 1978 (Box 23)
  - Gold Greenlees Trott, brochures, undated (Box 23)
  - Howard Agency
    - Company profile, undated (Box 23)
    - Situation summary, undated (Box 23)
  - Mammoth Pervasive & Bland, brochure, undated (Box 23)
  - Miscellaneous agencies
    - Brochures, undated, 2 folders (Box 23)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 24)
    - Clippings, 1972-1977 and undated (Box 24)
    - Correspondence, 1975-1986 (Box 24)
    - Out of Towners Exhibit, New York City, undated
      - (includes some McKinney & Silver materials) (Box 24)
    - Proofs and tearsheets, 1977-1989 and undated (Box 24)
  - Norman, Craig & Kummel, questionnaire response, 1976 (Box 24)
  - NH&S, strategic planning guide, 1981 (Box 24)
  - Ogilvy & Mather, annual report, 1973 (Box 24)
  - Rockwell & Associates (John Rockwell), company profile, 1979 (Box 24)
  - Scali, McCabe, Sloves, company profile, undated (Box 24)
  - Wells, Rich, Greene, Inc., Prospective on the Future, 1977 (Box 24)
- New Business, 1969-1990, 6 boxes
  Contains materials related to M&S's attempts to acquire new accounts. The bulk of the materials include drafts and scripts of general agency presentations designed for prospective clients. Also includes reference materials relating to these presentations and research reports relating to particular markets, such as cold relief, snack food, diet food, travel and tourism. Some materials document the agency's general strategies for acquiring new business. Also contains correspondence relating to specific accounts targetted by the agency, such as Porsche and Smith Airlines. Items arrived foldered and original folder titles were maintained.
  - Development, 1972-1987
    Subseries includes materials documenting the agency's approach to gaining new business, primarily including market research, strategy statements.
    - General files, 1972-1979, 2 folders (Box 25)
    - Brand Analysis manuscript, undated (Box 25)
    - British advertising, 1981 (Box 25)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 25)
    - Cough-Cold-Allergy Relief market, 1987 (Box 25)
    - Diet market research, 1973-1976 and undated (Box 25)
    - Direct mail proposal, undated (Box 25)
    - Marketing strategy, 1973, undated (Box 25)
    - Media plans, 1974-1978 (Box 25)
    - New business development plan, 1978 (Box 25)
    - New business list, 1986 (Box 25)
    - New business tactics, 1973 (Box 26)
    - New product development, 1972-1978 (Box 26)
    - New product schematic outline, undated (Box 26)
    - North Carolina travel and tourism analysis, 1987 (Box 26)
    - Porsche, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Positioning strategy, 1984 (Box 26)
    - Prospect List, undated (Box 26)
    - Public Broadcasting System, 1983-1984 (Box 26)
    - Smith Airlines, 1982 and undated (Box 26)
    - Snack market, undated (Box 26)
    - Strategic and tactical plans, 1981 (Box 26)
    - Strategy
      - Chart, undated (Box 26)
      - Selection of types, undated (Box 26)
  - Drafts, 1972-1979 and undated
    Contains drafts of general agency presentations and advertisements. Bulk of materials include McKinney's handwritten notes in which he experimented with agency slogans and general campaign concepts, particularly those which became the basis for the agency's flip chart presentations. Contains extensive materials related to the agency's Anatomy of Selling an Idea campaign, which referenced the life and work of artist Leonardo da Vinci. Most of the items arrived as ruled note pads, with reference materials and additional drafts interleaved. Perforated pages from legal pads were detached. Legal sized items were photocopied and reduced to letter size. Original order of notebook pages and interleaved items was maintained. Items were grouped into folders according to the notepad to which they were attached. The presentation's title was used as the folder title; where no title was available, the presentation's first words were used as folder title. Notepads containing sketches for multiple or unidentifiable presentations were detached, paperclipped and foldered as miscellaneous flip chart drafts or miscellaneous presentation drafts. Folders arranged alphabetically.
    - Agency copy direction, undated (Box 26)
    - Agency flip chart script revisions, undated (Box 26)
    - Agency positioning, Talent Goes Where the Money Flows, undated (Box 26)
    - Agency recruitment ads, 1976-1979 and undated (Box 26)
    - Agency resume, 1972-1973 and undated (Box 26)
    - Anatomy of Selling an Idea, undated, 2 folders (Box 27)
    - Attention Getting Originality, undated (Box 27)
    - Banking client presentations, undated (Box 27)
    - Company model and diagram, undated (Box 27)
    - Company profile drafts, undated (Box 27)
    - General presentation flip chart draft, undated (Box 27)
    - Market research presentation, undated (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous flip chart drafts, undated (Box 27)
    - Miscellaneous presentation drafts, undated, 4 folders (Box 28)
  - Presentations, 1969-1990 and undated
    Contains primarily typewritten scripts of general agency presentations given to prospective clients. Also contains slides relating to a general agency presentation. Where provided, original folder titles were maintained. Many items arrived loose and interspersed throughout the collection. These items were grouped either according to presentation title or according to the first few words of the title, and arranged alphabetically.
    - Account planning module script, 1990 (Box 28)
    - Agency flip chart presentation script, I Know You've Got Better Things, 1983 (Box 28)
    - Agency introductory presentation script, Before We Get Started, 1980-1988 (Box 28)
    - Agency introductory presentation, Perhaps the Best Way, undated (Box 29)
    - Creative presentation script, Is Anyone Out There Listening, 1979-1980 (Box 29)
    - Creative workshop speech, extra slides, 1983-1984 (Box 29)
    - Credentials presentation script, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Generic new product proposal, undated (Box 29)
    - Give Yourself a Presentation, undated (Box 29)
    - House info presentation, undated (Box 29)
    - Glassware market, undated (Box 29)
    - Introduction to M&S, Full Service In Depth Marketing, undated (Box 29)
    - Introductory agency flipcard presentation, undated (Box 29)
    - Introductory new business presentation, On Our Way Down Here, 1988 (Box 29)
    - Introductory presentation script, I'd Like to Tell You, 1990 (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous introductory presentation scripts, 1987 and undated (Box 29)
    - Miscellaneous presentations, undated (Box 30)
    - More Creative-Aggressive Approach to Advertising, Merchandizing and Sales Promotion, undated (Box 30)
    - Most Agencies Introduce Themselves with Samples of their Work, undated (Box 30)
    - New business presentation, Last Evening I Was Looking, 1989 (Box 30)
    - New business slide presentation, 1969 (Box 30)
    - New business strategy, How We Would Function On Your Behalf, undated (Box 30)
    - Slide presentation script, Picking An Agency, undated (Box 30)
    - Success Is More Than A Signed Contract, undated (Box 30)
    - Success, Like An Iceberg, undated (Box 30)
    - What Makes A Great Client, 1985 (Box 30)
  - Reports, 1977-1990
    Subseries includes reports of new business conferences, status and production. Original folder titles were maintained and items were arranged alphabetically.
    - New business conference reports, 1981-1986 (Box 30)
    - New business status report, 1990 (Box 30)
    - Production status review, 1977-1979 (Box 30)
- Printed Material, 1954-1990 and undated, 15 boxes
  Includes newsletters, promotional materials, periodicals, reports, and typographic manuals. Items were arranged alphabetically by title.
  - Association of National Advertisers, Current Advertiser Practices in Compensating Their Agencies, 1976 (Box 31)
  - Ad Business Report, 1986-1989 (Box 31)
  - Ad Daily Reprints, undated (Box 31)
  - Ad Day newsletter, 1978-1979, 1985 (Box 31)
  - Ad Hoc magazine, 1986 and undated (Box 31)
  - Arizona Portfolio, 1986 (Box 31)
  - Art Directors Club of Charlotte, programs, undated (Box 31)
  - Banking brochures, undated (Box 31)
  - Carolina Art Directors' Annual Exhibition, programs, undated (Box 31)
  - Chicago One Show, programs, 1967 (Box 31)
  - Cleveland Society of Communicating Arts, 17th Annual Exhibition, catalog, 1965 (Box 31)
  - Communication Graphics Exhibition, American Institute of Graphic Arts, 1967 (Box 31)
  - Dover Publications catalogues, undated (Box 31)
  - Event programs, 1987-1989 (Box 31)
  - Findings newsletter, 1966-1973 (Box 31)
  - Gallagher Report newsletter, 1975-1986 (Box 31)
  - Kiplinger Washington newsletter, 1972 (Box 31)
  - Management strategies, 1976-1977, 1985 and undated (Box 31)
  - Marketing research, 1956-1974 (Box 31)
  - Miscellaneous business tips, 1970-1974 (Box 32)
  - Miscellaneous printed matter, 1970-1990 (Box 32)
  - Periodicals, 1961-1990
    Contains periodicals related to advertising, marketing, commercial photography and graphic design. Items arrived loose and interspersed throughout the collection. Where multiple issues of publication were present, items were grouped and foldered by title. Single issues were foldered by subject category.
    - Ad Art Techniques, 1968 Nov. (Box 32)
    - Ads, 1983 Sept.-1985 Aug. (Box 32)
    - Adweek, 1981 Aug.-1990 Oct. (Box 33)
    - Adweek Creative Services Directory, 1982 (Box 33)
    - Adweek's Winners, 1987-1989 (Box 33)
    - American Artists, 1961 Mar. (Box 33)
    - Archive: Ads, T.V. & Posters Worldwide, 1985 (Box 33)
    - Art Direction: The Magazine of Creative Advertising
      - 1961 Jan.-1969 July (Box 34)
      - 1972 June-1979 Sept. (Box 35)
      - 1980 Apr.-1985 Dec. (Box 36)
      - 1986 Jan.-1987 Dec. (Box 37)
      - 1988 Jan.-1989 Dec. (Box 38)
      - 1990 Jan.-1990 Dec. (Box 39)
    - Gebrauchsgraphik International Advertising Art, 1964 July-1969 Apr. (Box 40)
    - Miscellaneous advertising trade magazine issues, 1972-1978 (Box 41)
    - Omni, collector's edition, 1978 Oct. (Box 41)
    - Photo design periodicals, 1967, 1980, 1987 (Box 41)
    - Southern Advertising Markets, 1972 Jan.; 1974 Aug.; 1976 Feb. (Box 41)
    - Vista: Magazine of the United Nations Association, 1972 Sept.-Oct. (Box 41)
  - Promotional materials, 1969-1987
    Contains promotional pamphlets, brochures and take-away-cards sent by particular companies and graphic artists hoping to gain the business of M&S. Items arrived loose and interspersed throughout the collection. In cases where multiple brochures were present from a particular company, items were foldered by company. All other items were foldered as miscellaneous promotional material.
    - CBS News, 1973 and undated (Box 41)
    - Diagnostic Research, Inc., undated (Box 41)
    - Fortune Magazine, Rhyme of the Ancient Manager, 1969 (Box 41)
    - Four by Five stock photography, 1978-1982 (Box 41)
    - Hammermill Paper Parlor, undated, 2 folders (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous promotional material, undated, 5 folders (Box 41)
    - Miscellaneous promotional material, undated, 6 folders (Box 42)
    - Miscellaneous promotional material, undated, 6 folders (Box 43)
    - Miscellaneous promotional material, undated (Box 44)
    - Sotheby's International Realty, Portfolio of Distinctive Properties, 1987 (Box 44)
  - Psychology Today, Dictionary of Advertising Terms, undated (Box 44)
  - Rubel Service, 1962-1989 (Box 44)
  - Show, The, 1982 (Box 44)
  - South Carolina National Corporation, Annual Report, 1976 (Box 44)
  - Tax-related printed material, 1954-1979 (Box 44)
  - Typography, 1983 and undated
    - Alphatype Corporation, 1983 (Box 45)
    - Letraset, undated (Box 45)
    - Photo-Headlines, undated (Box 45)
    - Techni-Process, Inc., undated (Box 45)
  - Out of Towners Advertising Exhibit, 1986 (Box 46)
    - Cardboard book (Box 46)
    - Photocopy of cardboard packaging (Box 46)
- Writings and Speeches, 1952-1990 and undated, 3 boxes
  Contains speeches given by McKinney and other advertising executives at various events. Also includes reports prepared by outside agencies on general advertising and business-related topics which McKinney used as reference. Items were foldered and labelled according to speech title and arranged alphabetically.
  - Speeches by McKinney, 1952-1987 and undated (Box 47)
    - Advertising's Moment of Truth, 1974, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - Celebrities speech, undated (Box 47)
    - Competing With The Giants, 1983 (Box 47)
    - Even a Pope Can Be a Bad Client, undated (Box 47)
    - Issue Advertising, undated (Box 47)
    - Magazine Advertising Representatives of the South speech materials, 1975 (Box 47)
    - Magazine Day speech, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Magazine Publisher's Association Award speech, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Manager's speech, 1987 (Box 47)
    - Miscellaneous short speeches, undated (Box 47)
    - Power of Print, undated (Box 47)
    - Sales speech reference materials, 1952-1975 and undated (Box 47)
  - Reports by others, 1966-1988 and undated
    - Agency-Client Reports, Executive Communications, undated (Box 47)
    - Concept Testing, undated (Box 47)
    - Contemporary Planning Methodology for Toro, undated (Box 48)
    - Corporate Analysis: A General Framework for Diagnosis, McKinsey & Co., 1972 (Box 48)
    - Cost Control and Profit Responsibility, 1966 (Box 48)
    - Effective Marketing Management, 1973 (Box 48)
    - Evaluating New Product Proposals, Conference Board, 1973 (Box 48)
    - Handbook of Independent Advertising and Marketing Services, 1973 (Box 48)
    - How to Value a Service Business, 1988 and undated (Box 48)
    - Marketing: How Many Dimensions, American Bankers Association, 1971 (Box 48)
    - Marketing Studies, Executive Communications, Inc., undated (Box 48)
    - Multivariate Procedures in Marketin g, L. Percy, undated (Box 48)